A temptingly tasteful comedy for adults who can count.
10 is a comedy, romance film directed by Blake Edwards.
A Hollywood songwriter goes through a mid-life crisis and
becomes infatuated with a sexy blonde newlywed.
George Webber, played by Dudley Moore.
Samantha Taylor, played by Julie Andrews.
Jenny Hanley, played by Bo Derek.
Hugh, played by Robert Webber.
Mary Lewis, played by Dee Wallace.
David Hanley, played by Sam J. Jones.
10 is a 1979 American romantic comedy film written, produced and directed by Blake
Edwards and starring Dudley Moore, Julie Andrews, Robert Webber, and Bo Derek.
It was considered a trendsetting film at the time of its release and
became one of the year's biggest box-office hits.
The film follows middle-aged composer George Webber who becomes infatuated with Jenny
Hanley, a newlywed young woman he has never met, and pursues her to Mexico.
The film explores themes of beach, mexico, midlife crisis, honeymoon, crisis.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.